Zongzhen (Jack) Yang

Highly motivated Computer Science and Communication Arts student with 6+ years' experience in VR/AR. A passionate team player who strives to make a difference in how people perceive the world and eagers to gain new experience.

jackyangzzh@gmail.com 862-400-3570 thejackyang.com

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - MADISON

B.A. in Computer Science & Communication Arts

Teaching Assistant for CS559 Computer Graphics (Fall 2019 & Spring 2020)

SETON HALL PREPARATORY SCHOOL

National Honor Society

SKILLS

Virtual Reality

Unity • Leap Motion • Open VR • Oculus • Data Visualization • VR Design • Social VR • Blender • THREE.js • Motion Tracking • ARkit • ARCore • Vuforia

Programming Languages

C# • Java • JavaScript • Flutter • HTML • MATLAB • Latex • Swift • Git • C++

User Experience Design

Interaction Design • Usability Testing • Sketch • Adobe XD • Photoshop • 3D UX Design

Communication

Team Communication • Public Speaking • Presentation • Negotiation • Cross-cultural Communication • Virtual Communication

COURSE WORK

Computer Science

Computer Graphics
Data Visualization
Virtual Reality Specialization
Wearable Technology
User Experience Design
Game Design
Software Engineering

Communication Arts

Persuasion and Speeches Online Communication Transmedia Storytelling Dale Carnegie Training

RESEARCH

KATS LABATORY OF APPLIED PHYSICS

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

October 2017 - Present

- Design different algorithms to simulate different color visions including colorblindness
- Create and program Virtual Reality spaces to visualize research findings through color calibrated VR headsets

UW COMPUTER GRAPHICS LAB

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

September 2019 - May 2020

- Design remote mimicry control of robot arms with Vive controller in an Unity simulation environment
- Design and perform experiments that study the performance of various feedback when remote controlling robot arms

UW HUMAN COMPUTER INTERACTION LAB

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

April 2017 - November 2017

- · Work on a robot that help elementary school children to read
- Develop an algorithm that rank books the readers are mostly likely to be interested in based on history and preferences
- Collaborate with engineers to add speech recognition and feedback features to robots

EXPERIENCE

HOLOS

UNITY DEVELOPER INTERN

May 2019 - Now

- Work with Unity and Leap Motion hand tracking to develop Virtual Reality platform for interactive learning
- Collaborate with CTO and co-founder to design, prototype, implement, and maintain interaction mechanics such as virtual objects and augmented gestures
- · Develop virtual reality ad campaigns for the company

CARNEGIE MELLON UNIVERSITY GAME ACADEMY PRODUCT MANAGER & DEVELOPER

May 2015 - August 2015

- Develop two arcade-inspired game and an interactive Virtual Reality called Kitchen Kraving (soon to be published on Oculus store)
- Work with Maya to create 3D models and implement player interaction with Unity to create realistic player's virtual experience